[{"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Approximately how much does a typical female vampire bat weigh?", "correct_answer": "1.5 oz.", "incorrect_answers": ["8 oz.", "5 oz.", "1 lb."]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "This 1989 movie is about  Bob and Diane, drug-driven Bonnie and Clyde, who rob drugstores to finance their habit.", "correct_answer": "Drugstore Cowboy", "incorrect_answers": ["The Little Mermaid", "My Left Foot", "Checking Out"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Which of these is the first family in movie history that includes three different Oscar winners?", "correct_answer": "Garland/Minnellis", "incorrect_answers": ["Barrymores", "Baldwins", "Fondas"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Which Star Wars character said, Luke, I am your father.?", "correct_answer": "Darth Vader", "incorrect_answers": ["The Emperor", "Count Dooku", "Darth Maul"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "What is the other common name of the punk Mohawk hairstyle?", "correct_answer": "Mohican", "incorrect_answers": ["Pompadour", "Mop-Top", "All of these"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Who popularized the song Unforgettable in 1951?", "correct_answer": "Nat King Cole", "incorrect_answers": ["Humphrey Bogart", "Dean Martin", "Frank Sinatra"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "After meeting to discuss heading back to port busted, Capt. Billy Tyne informs the crew they are heading to what location in search of more and bigger fish?", "correct_answer": "The Flemish Cap", "incorrect_answers": ["The Atlantic Canyon", "The Atlantic Reef", "The Grand Banks"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "In the film The Crow, what is the relation between Top Dollar and Myca?", "correct_answer": "Brother and sister", "incorrect_answers": ["Husband and wife", "Boss and employee", "None"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "The birthstone of this month is the emerald, and its birth flower is Lily of the Valley.", "correct_answer": "May", "incorrect_answers": ["July", "September", "November"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "What breed was the first canine movie star, Rin Tin Tin?", "correct_answer": "German Shepherd", "incorrect_answers": ["Border Collie", "Labrador", "Greyhound"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Which type of mirror produces an image that is smaller than the original?", "correct_answer": "Concave", "incorrect_answers": ["Convex", "Flat", "Concave-Convex"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "What does the store clerk in the movie Fight Club want to be?", "correct_answer": "A veterinarian", "incorrect_answers": ["A doctor", "A lawyer", "A store owner"]}]